empressgist.com 2017-12-26

# PRIVACY POLICY – EMPRESS GIST

1\. All User information supplied by Users of Empressgist.com as defined under this Terms & Conditions is covered by the Data Protection Act 1998.  
2\. Users can amend information provided at any time by contacting [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)  
3\. Users can access the data held on them by Empressgist.com by contacting us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)  
4\. User information will not be disclosed to a third party without Users’ permission. User details will be used only to provide service(s) specifically requested by the User.  
5\. Users’ details may be transferred to another company if ownership of Empressgist.com changes.  
6\. The Empressgist.com website uses cookies. Users may choose not to accept cookies but this will prevent proper functioning of the services of the website.  
7\. Whenever a User requests a page, username, IP address, browser and version of operating system are stored in a log file. This information is only used for statistical purposes to help improve this site and provide accurate statistics to advertisers in the form of aggregated data.  
8\. Empressgist.com Limited cannot guarantee that third party services accessible through Empressgist.com services operate the same Privacy Policy.  
9\. Empressgist.com Limited reserves the right to update and change this Privacy Policy at any time. However, Empressgist.com Limited will not use information submitted by a User under this current notice in a way not currently described herein without also notifying the User of such change, and giving the User an opportunity to opt-out, or otherwise prevent that new use of your information.  
10\. If you have any questions concerning this Privacy Policy or would like us to amend or do away with your details please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

 **Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.
